#### **ABOUT ME**

My 8 years of experience in HR has allowed me to develop exceptional skills in different areas; project management, communication, event management, analytical thinking, and maintain company's culture, vision and mission among employees.

I look forward to contribute Positively in a highly motivated environment, to utilize my capabilities and skills to the fullest.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### **BACHELOR OF SCIENCE**

King Saud University / Riyadh /

B.S Business Administration.

#### **SKILLS**

COMMUNICATION

PROBLEM SOLVING

**TEAMWORK** 

**FLEXIBILITY** 

**CREATIVITY** 

LEADERSHIP AND MANAGEMENT

### **LANGUAGES**

ARABIC

**ENGLISH** 

# ARWA A. ALABDULLATIF



Riyadh



+966500004173



arwa.alabdullatiff@gmail.com

#### Work Experience

#### MINISTRY OF **INVESTMENT (MISA)**

Rivadh

Sep 2021 - Present

# **Change Management & Communication Specialist**

- -Develops and evaluating a communication strategy. -Provide creative support for internal program communication efforts.
- -Assess organizational readiness and develops change management strategies and plans that maximize employee adoption and usage and minimize resistance.
- -Manages the initiatives and activities covered in the change management and communication plans and develops the content required to execute them.
- -Protect and enhance organization reputation to support key business objectives and growth.
- -Manages, planning and coordinating the department efforts.
- -Organizes major events.

#### MINISTRY OF **INVESTMENT (MISA)**

Aug 2019 - Sep 2021

#### Senior HR Strategy and Culture

- -Project manage the implementa on of different policies, objec ves and events such as applying changes on the end of service policies and collabora ng with different organiza ons to do employees yearly gathering.
- -Coordinate planning and budge ng ac vi es to meet required Company melines.
- -Ensure that all aspects of the HR func on promote an organiza onal culture of teamwork and service, high quality, transparency and accountability, innova on and inclusiveness.
- -Deliver on mul ple ad-hoc project requests requiring the need for strong project management, collabora on, and communica on skills.
- -Key responsibili es include engagement with culture champions, communica ons and session logis cs.
- -Work with PR team to evaluate adver sing HR promo onal programs to ensure they align with PR and HR goals.
- -Develop and launch internal announcements.

#### **GENERAL INVESTMENT AUTHORITY (SAGIA)**

Riyadh Nov 2018 - Jun 2019

### Senior HR Officer

- -Assist the HR Manager with Job Evaluation/Analysis.
- -Responsible for the execution of HR services in the areas of employees' welfare administrations.
- -In collaboration with the HR team, develop the HR Calendar and objectives for the year.
- -Provides support to employees in the interpretation of HR policies and guidelines.
- -To always monitor current processes and identify ways to improve these processes and systems.
- -Prepares the reports which identify areas that need improvement within the organization.
- -Seek opportunities for partnerships, sponsorships for some of -Collaborate with marketing and maintain open communication
- with senior management. -Organises and manages special client events, such as open days

#### **GENERAL INVESTMENT AUTHORITY (SAGIA)**

Rivadh

Aug 2015 - Nov 2018

# Associate HR Specialist

and conferences.

- -Processing and updating employment records related to hiring, transferring, promoting, and terminating.
- -Enrolls new employees by issuing forms and applications; verifying completion and explaining benefit programs.
- -Explaining human resources policies, procedures, laws, and standards to new and existing employees.
- -Performing job evaluations and job analyses.
- -Overseeing engagement programs and other employee relations work.

HR Administrative Assistant

#### **AL KHALEEJ TRAINING AND EDUCATION** Riyadh Mar 2014 - Jun 2015

# COURSES

**MERCER** Sep 2018

**MEIRC** Nov 2017 International Position Evaluation

Skills for HR Management Professional

## **UNIVERSITY COLLEGE OF PROFESSIONAL STUDIES**

Jan 2017

GEORGE WASHINGTON 

Key Performance Indictor Associate (KPI-A)

Nov 2016 - Nov 2017

# **Train the Trainers**

**English E-language Program** 

## HRD TRAINING AND DEVELOPMENT.

Apr 2016

# MEIRC

Dec 2016

# Recruitment, Interviewing & Selection

**SAUDI ARAMCO** Nov 2016

**Developing Woman Competencies at Work** 

**JODAYN** 

Nov 2016

**Business Process Management**